Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Edward G. Wilson Papers, 1906-1991, bulk 1946-1971 RL.00758
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files Series, 1939-1975, 10 boxes
  - Executive Committee
    - Agenda, 1958-1972, 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Kohl, Howard, 1958-1963 (See also Oversize Box 90), 4 folders (Box 70)
    - Wilson, E.G., 1962-1964 (See also Oversize Box 90), 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Eyes on Thompson program, 1965 (Box 71)
  - General information book about JWT, 1949-1961 (Box 71)
  - Getting On in Advertising, undated (Box 71)
  - House agencies, 1958 (Box 71)
  - Hunter Richley's Hundred Rules for Being a Business Man, undated (Box 71)
  - Improvement program for JWT, 1963 (See also Oversize Box 90) (Box 71)
  - Information Center, 1964 (Box 71)
  - Interlease, 1971 (Box 71)
  - International agency competitors, 1965 (Box 71)
  - International brochure, 1965 (Box 71)
  - International organization of JWT, 1942-1967 (Box 71)
  - JWT in Southeast Asia, 1966 (Box 71)
  - JWT News (Box 72)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1968 (Box 72)
    - Survey, 1950-1964 (Box 72)
  - Latin American managers' meeting, 1968 (Box 72)
  - McDonald's investment, 1968-1970 (Box 72)
  - Management Committee: H. Kohl's notes, 1955-1958 (See also Oversize Box 90), 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Managers' meetings, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 72)
  - Market research: Italy, 1969 (Box 72)
  - Meek, Sam: claim to office furnishings, 1963-1972 (Box 72)
  - Myth and Reality in the Advertising Agency Business, JWT presentation, 1978 (Box 72)
  - National Business Council for Consumer Affairs, 1971 (Box 72)
  - Nature of Advertising Knowledge, speech by James Webb Young, 1954 (Box 72)
  - New York office position report by accounts, 1970 (Box 73)
  - New York Operation Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 73)
  - Objectives and principles of operation, 1949-1966 (Box 73)
  - Population and its Distribution, 1960-1961 (Box 73)
  - Price Waterhouse recommendations, 1962-1971 (Box 73)
  - Profit planning, 1968 (Box 73)
  - Promotion Group operating plan, 1969 (Box 73)
  - Puerto Rican-American Insurance Company, 1965-1968 (Box 73)
  - Review Board, 1949-1968 (Box 73)
  - Speeches of Rena Bartos, 1976 (Box 73)
  - Talks on Building Advertising, ca. 1920 (Box 73)
  - Thompson Man, story by Chris Cross, 1968 (Box 73)
  - Volunteer accounts, 1966-1968 (Box 74)
- Financial Files Series, 1930-1971 (RESTRICTED), 3 boxes
  Includes Finance Committee minutes and background materials. The files listed under foreign accounting practice reveal the operation as well as the organization of the regional offices. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Billings, 1961-1968 (Box 74)
  - Breed, Abbot & Morgan, Time on JWT matters, 1963-1971 (Box 74)
  - Consolidated balance sheet, 1961-1970 (See also Oversize Box 91), 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Diversification, 1962-1968 (Box 74)
  - Finance Committee minutes, 1962-1965, 5 folders (Box 74)
  - Financial Department organization, 1957-1969 (Box 74)
  - Financial statements
    - Audited, 1966-1970 (Box 74)
    - JWT Fund, 1966-1970 (Box 74)
  - Foreign accounting practice (Box 75)
    - Argentina, 1934-1944 (See also Oversize box 91) (Box 75)
    - Australia, 1943-1944 (Box 75)
    - Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 75)
    - Export media, 1944 (Box 75)
    - India, 1946 (Box 75)
    - Local expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 75)
    - London reorganization, 1946-1952 (See also Oversize Box 91), 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Operating results
      - 1959-1964, A-V, 3 folders (Box 75)
      - 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Profit sharing, 1932-1945 (Box 75)
  - Formula price of common stock, 1944-1954 (Box 75)
  - Furniture and improvements, 1943-1954 (Box 75)
  - Memberships, 1968-1969 (Box 75)
  - Out-of-pocket costs, 1970 (Box 75)
  - Profitability trends, 1967-1968 (See also Oversize Box 91) (Box 75)
  - Reorganization, 1947-1955 (Box 75)
  - Salaries, 1945 (Restricted materials removed) (Box 76)
- Personnel Files Series, 1906-1971 (RESTRICTED), 4 boxes
  Divided into three categories--General, Individuals, and Offices. The General category includes materials on organization and management, employee statistics and salary expenditures. The Individuals category, containing biographical information, clippings, and correspondence, is arranged in alphabetical order by last name. The Offices category, listing biographical information for office managers and staff, is arranged in alphabetical order by name of the country in which the office is located.
  - General (Box 76)
    - Apprentices and trainees, 1949 (Box 76)
    - Basic management objectives in personnel administration, undated (Box 76)
    - Board of Directors and Executive Committee, 1950-1969 (Box 76)
    - Board resolutions (retirement and death), M-Y, 1952-1969 (Box 76)
    - Citizenship of personnel in international offices, 1964 (Box 76)
    - Management group, 1949 (Box 76)
    - Medical services (JWT Clinic operations), 1968-1971 (Box 76)
    - Military leaves of absence, 1968-1971 (Restricted materials removed) (Box 76)
    - Numbers and salaries (See also Oversize Boxes 91, 91)
      - Domestic, 1906-1970 (Box 76)
      - International, 1930-1956 (Box 76)
    - Number by office, 1906-1963 (Box 76)
    - Number of officers and directors, 1945-1971 (Box 76)
    - Officer lists, 1947-1970 (Box 76)
    - Organization and management
      - Domestic, 1952-1959 (Box 76)
      - Domestic, 1960-1969, 2 folders (Box 77)
      - International, 1958-1969 (Box 77)
    - Personnel in New York Office with overseas experience, 1965 (Box 77)
    - Personnel lists
      - Chicago, 1924-1946 (Box 77)
      - Cincinnati, 1932 (Box 77)
      - Detroit, 1946 (Restricted materials removed) (Box 77)
      - New York, 1906-1924, 1929-1945, 3 folders (Box 77)
      - St. Louis, 1932-1939 (Box 77)
      - West coast, 1932-1950 (Box 77)
    - Personnel statistics, 1968-1970 (Box 77)
    - Physical examination for executives, 1950-1967 (Box 77)
      Preventive medicine benefits plans
  - Individuals
    - Black, George, 1963-1965 (Box 77)
    - Brundage, Howard D., 1972 (Box 77)
    - Campbell-Harris, David, 1962 (Box 77)
    - Castilo, Branc, R.P., 1965-1968 (Box 77)
    - Clark, Howard F., 1959-1964 (Box 77)
    - Doyer, Bob, 1964-1968 (Box 77)
    - Dunham, Peter, 1961 (Box 78)
    - Erskina, William H., 1965 (Box 78)
    - Fedderman, Marjorie, 1967-1968 (Box 78)
    - Glah, Roy, 1964-1968 (Box 78)
    - Johnston, G. Donald, 1959-1966 (Box 78)
    - Kinney, Gilbert, 1941 (Box 78)
    - Lanigan, Denis, 1963-1964 (Box 78)
    - Moskowitz, Milton, 1966-1968 (Box 78)
    - Morrison, Alexander, 1964 (Box 78)
    - Morrison, Julian, 1965 (Box 78)
    - Perdomo, Luis A., 1965 (Box 78)
    - Pettingrew, John A., 1965 (Box 78)
    - Saunders, Douglas, and Rodgers, John, 1958-1960 (Box 78)
    - Senior, Raimond, 1965 (Box 78)
    - Sharman, Jenn L., 1964-1965 (Box 78)
    - Souhami, Gerald, 1962-1965 (Box 78)
    - Stridsberg, Albert, 1963-1968 (Box 78)
    - Thayer, John E., 1963-1965 (See also Oversize Box 91) (Box 78)
    - Wallace, Robert D., 1964 (Box 78)
    - Watt, Andrew MacLean, 1963-1965 (Box 78)
    - Webster, J.G.O., 1965 (Box 78)
    - Young, James W., 1956 (Box 78)
  - Offices
    - Argentina, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Australia, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Brazil, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Canada, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Chile, Colombia, 1962 (Box 78)
    - France, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Germany, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Great Britain, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Holland, 1962 (Box 78)
    - India, 1962 (Box 78)
    - Italy, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Japan, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Mexico, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Pakistan, Panama, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Peru, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Philippines, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Puerto Rico, 1962 (Box 79)
    - Venezuela, 1962 (Box 79)
- Domestic Policies and Procedures Series, 1941-1987, 3 boxes
  Includes procedures and guidelines for the operation of JWT North American offices. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Account team procedures, 1963-1987 (Box 79)
  - Advertising budget requirement, 1962 (Box 79)
  - Advertising controls, 1942-1947 (Box 79)
  - Attendance guidelines, 1970 (Box 79)
  - Audience measurement standards, 1963 (Box 79)
  - Bank accounts, 1942 (Box 79)
  - Billings and compensation, 1947-1965 (Box 79)
  - Client authorization, 1949-1957 (Box 79)
  - Clients' products, 1956 (Box 79)
  - Collateral work, 1950-1959 (Box 79)
  - Common stock distribution, 1954-1970 (Box 79)
  - Communications, 1949-1964 (Box 79)
  - Consumer proposition, 1957 (Box 79)
  - Contributions, 1957-1961 (Box 79)
  - Creative procedures, 1960-1965 (Box 79)
  - Data processing, 1941-1973 (Box 79)
  - Employee evaluation program, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Field representatives, 1956 (Box 79)
  - General expenses, 1948-1958 (Box 79)
  - Group health insurance, 1957-1970 (Box 79)
  - Hard-liquor accounts, 1956-1963 (Box 79)
  - History of accounts, 1960-1971 (Box 80)
  - Holidays, 1961-1965 (Box 80)
  - JWT forward planning, 1964 (Box 80)
  - Leave of absence, 1959-1961 (Box 80)
  - Loans to employees, 1970 (Box 80)
  - Marketing-merchandising activities, 1948-1963 (Box 80)
  - Media contracts, 1942-1950 (Box 80)
  - Media operations, 1956-1957 (Box 80)
  - Military leaves of absence, 1959-1970 (Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous office policies, 1946-1966 (Box 80)
  - New business presentations, 1957-1966 (Box 80)
  - Officers, 1942-1971 (Box 80)
  - Petty cash vouchers, 1960 (Box 80)
  - Plan & data record, 1960 (Box 80)
  - Policy decisions, 1955 (Box 80)
  - Political activities, 1960-1968 (Box 80)
  - Profit-Sharing Trust, 1955-1967 (Box 80)
  - Public relations, 1957-1968 (Box 80)
  - Purchasing, 1963 (Box 80)
  - Representatives, 1956-1957 (Box 80)
  - Research, 1956-1966 (Box 80)
  - Research projects, 1948-1966 (Box 81)
  - Retirement, 1962-1972 (Box 81)
  - Review Board, 1956-1964 (Box 81)
  - Sale of obsolete printing plates, 1950 (Box 81)
  - Salary payments, 1971 (Box 81)
  - Speeches and articles, 1953-1963 (Box 81)
  - Taxes, 1942 (Box 81)
  - Television terminology, 1963 (Box 81)
  - Trade conventions, 1961-1963 (Box 81)
  - Traffic Department, 1960 (Box 81)
  - Travel expenses, 1946-1966 (Box 81)
  - Unsolicited ideas, 1962 (Box 81)
  - Vacations, 1957-1971 (Box 81)
- International Policies and Procedures Series, 1930-1967, 1 box
  Includes procedures and guidelines for the operation of JWT international offices. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Agency-client relationships, 1966-1967 (Box 81)
  - Awards & contests, 1950-1965 (Box 81)
  - Competitive accounts, 1959-1960 (Box 81)
  - Corporate advertising, 1964 (Box 81)
  - Creative philosophy, 1966 (Box 81)
  - Foreign accounting practices, 1930-1934 (Box 81)
  - Large vs. small agencies, 1955-1957 (Box 81)
  - Policy control in World-Wide business, 1958 (Box 81)
  - Stock, 1957-1962 (Box 81)
  - Unsolicited ideas, 1962 (Box 81)
  - World-wide advertising, 1958-1964 (Box 81)
- Writings and Speeches Series, 1941-1987, 2 boxes
  Contains primarily speeches given by Wilson, including several made after his retirement. Arranged alphabetically.
  - Speeches, 1941-1987, 5 folders (Box 82)
  - Talks to representatives
    - 1963 Mar., Folder 1 of 2 (Box 82)
    - 1963 Mar., Folder 2 of 2 (Box 83)
    - 1967 Jan. (Box 83)
  - Year-end talks, 1960-1963 (See also Oversize Box 91) (Box 83)
- Personal Files Series, 1930-1991, 4 boxes
  Primarily correspondence, interviews and articles about Wilson, clippings, and personal financial records. Much of the material reflects Wilson's ongoing relationship with JWT after his retirement. Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - 1088 Park Ave. Corporation, 1972 (Box 83)
  - Application for employment, 1930 (Box 83)
  - Appraisal of N. Strouse books sent to Duke, 1990 (Box 83)
  - Birthday greetings, 1971-1979 (Box 83)
  - Correspondence, 1949-1991
    - Collated, 1971-1987, 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Collated, 1988-1990 (Box 84)
    - Duke University, 1987-1991 (Box 84)
    - JWT archives, 1978-1982 (Box 84)
    - Kuhl, Cal, 1972 (Box 84)
    - Swank, Cynthia, 1989-1990 (Box 84)
    - Wilson, Jane, 1949-1971 (Box 84)
  - Criminal background report for immigration to France, 1962 (Box 84)
  - Diaries
    - 1938-1940, 2 folders (Box 84)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 85)
  - Effect of Current and Future Economic Developments on Advertising and Marketing, 1974 (Box 85)
  - Interviews
    - Hinks, K., 1979-1982 (Box 85)
    - Kohl, H., 1979 (Box 85)
    - Wilson, E.G., 1979 (Box 85)
  - J. Walter Thompson Company
    - Annual meetings notices, 1973-1985 (Box 85)
    - CIA link, 1975 (Box 85)
    - Historical project, 1972-1978 (Box 85)
    - TV syndication unit scandal, 1982 (Box 85)
    - United States Stamps, undated (Box 85)
      [Album of postage stamps designed by JWT artists.]
  - Miscellaneous notes, 1971-1990 (See also Oversize Box 91) (Box 86)
  - News clippings, 1982-1989 (Box 86)
  - Personal profit-sharing account
    - Correspondence, 1940-1974 (Box 86)
    - Statements, 1934-1972 (Box 86)
  - Published articles about E.G. Wilson, 1972-1987 (Box 86)
  - Records transfer memos, 1967-1977 (Box 86)
  - Tributes to Norman Strouse, 1969-1990 (Box 86)
  - WPP takeover, 1989 (Box 86)
- Oversize Materials, 4 boxes
  - International Offices Series, 1933-1966
    - Great Britain (London) (Box 89)
      - Articles of Association, 1933-1951 (Box 89)
      - Corporate documentation, 1933-1966 (Box 89)
      - Pension plan, 1965 Sept. (Box 89)
      - Public relations for advertising (Lexington International), 1966 June (Box 89)
      - Reorganization, 1956-1961 (Box 89)
      - Royal Commission on the Press, 1961 (Box 89)
    - India
      - Articles of Association and Certificate of Incorporation, 1938 Mar. (Box 89)
      - Restriction on advertising expenditure, 1965 Mar.- Apr. (Box 89)
    - Ireland
      - Proposed Articles of Association, 1939 (Box 89)
    - South Africa
      - Correspondence (operation of company), 1956 Aug.-Dec. (Box 89)
      - Financial statements, 1954-1961 (Box 89)
      - Memorandum of Association, Articles of Association, Certificate of Incorporation, 1954 (Box 89)
    - Spain
      - Correspondence, vol. II, 1965 Mar.-July (Box 89)
  - Trip Files Series, 1954-1964
    - 1954 Feb.: Europe (Box 89)
    - 1961 July: London (Box 89)
    - 1962 July: Europe (Box 89)
    - 1963
      - Jan.: Europe (Box 89)
      - Apr.: Europe (Box 90)
      - June: Europe (Box 90)
      - Nov.: Europe (Box 90)
    - 1964
      - Feb.: Europe (Box 90)
      - Mar.: India, Pakistan, Tokyo (Box 90)
  - Legal Files Series, 1927-1971
    - Financial incentives, vol. II, 1951-1960 (Box 90)
    - JWT stock
      - Resor stock interests (purchase of Mrs. Resor's B stocks), 1960 (Box 90)
    - Lawsuits
      - Laemmar & Sartoris vs. JWT
        - Brief and depositions, 1969-1971 (Box 90)
        - Supporting documents taken to trial, 1972 May (Box 90)
        - Worksheets of stock purchases, 1964-1969 (Box 90)
    - Labor matters, 1950-1953 (Box 90)
    - Letters of terms
      - Sylvania-Corning Nuclear Corp., 1957 (Box 90)
    - Radio productions
      - Edgar Bergen, Standard Brands show, 1941-1942 (Box 90)
    - Resor, Stanley
      - S. & H. Resor trusts (indentures and amendments), 1927-1960 (Box 90)
    - Television
      - Ford Motor Company, James Melton package, vol. III, 1951 (Box 90)
    - Television Writers of America
      - Labor Relations Board, 1953 (Box 90)
  - Subject Files Series, 1955-1964
    - Executive Committee (Box 90)
      - Kohl, Howard, 1958-1959 (Box 90)
      - Wilson, E.G., 1964 (Box 90)
    - Improvement program for JWT (hiring of H. Schacte), 1963 (Box 90)
    - Management Committee
      - Kohl, H. Notes, 1955-1958 (Box 90)
    - JWT organization and management, 1960-1961 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Financial Files Series, 1946-1970
    - Consolidated Balance sheet, 1959-1970 (Box 91)
    - Foreign accounting practice: London reorganization, 1946-1952 (Box 91)
    - Profitability trends, 1967-1968 (Box 91)
  - Personnel Files Series, 1906-1965
    - General Subseries (Box 91)
      - Numbers and salaries (domestic), 1906-1963 (Box 91)
    - Individuals Subseries
      - Thayer, John E., 1963-1965 (Box 91)
  - Writings and Speeches Series, 1960-1963
    - Year-end talks, 1960-1963 (Box 91)
  - Personal Files Series, 1971-1974
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1971-1974 (Box 91)
    - Retirement gift (poster), Notes for a Yellow Legal Pad, 1972 (Oversize-folder 2)
  - Financial Files Series, 1930-1944
    - Foreign accounting practice (Box 91)
      - Argentina, 1934-1944 (Box 91)
      - Local expenses, 1930-1931 (Box 91)
  - Personnel Files Series, 1906-1962
    - General (Box 91)
      - Numbers and salaries (domestic), 1906-1962 (Box 91)
  - Legal Files Series, 1942-1946
    - Standard contract paragraph index, 1942-1946 (Box 92)
- Restricted Materials, 3 boxes
  Sensitive personnel materials pertaining to individual employee matters, pulled from other series. Closed to non-JWT users until 2045. Arranged according to the original series and folder order.
  - International Offices Series (Box RS1)
    - Australia
      - Brisbane--Correspondence, 1961 May-Aug. (Box RS1)
        Items pulled from Box 1.
      - Deferred compensation plan, 1960-1962, 2 folders (Box RS1)
      - Melbourne--Sam Meek files, 1957-1961 (Box RS1)
    - Austria
      - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box RS1)
    - Belgium (Antwerp)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box RS1)
      - Salaries, 1965 (Box RS1)
    - Brazil
      - Rio de Janeiro correspondence, 1955-1962 (Box RS1)
      - São Paulo
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1961-1962 (Box RS1)
          - General, 1969-1971 (Box RS1)
            Items pulled from Box 2.
          - Volume I, 1949-1962 (Box RS1)
          - Volume II, 1963-1967 (Box RS1)
        - Sam Meek files, 1957-1961 (Box RS1)
    - Canada
      - Montreal
        - Sam Meek files, 1954-1959 (Box RS1)
        - Sam Meek files, 1960-1963 (Box RS1)
          Items pulled from Box 3.
      - Vancouver correspondence, 1956-1965 (Box RS1)
    - Chile (Santiago)
      - Background information, 1963 (Box RS1)
      - Correspondence, 1960-1965 (Box RS1)
      - Sam Meek files, 1943-1961 (Box RS1)
    - Colombia (Bogotá)
      - Correspondence, 1953-1966 (Box RS1)
      - Report on trip by W. Lee Preschel, 1965 (Box RS1)
    - France (Paris)
      - Acquisition of another business, 1964-1965 (Box RS1)
      - Correspondence--Sam Meek files, 1944-1953 (Box RS1)
      - Correspoondence--Sam Meek files, 1954-1962, 10 folders (Box RS1)
        Items pulled from Box 4.
      - Personnel resignations and problems, 1962-1964 (Box RS1)
        Items pulled from Box 5.
      - Reorganization of company, 1962-1967, 3 folders (Box RS1)
    - Germany (Frankfurt)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1967, 2 folders (Box RS1)
      - Pensions, profit-sharing, salaries, and insurance, 1960-1965 (Box RS1)
    - Great Britain (London) (Box RS2)
      - Correspondence, 1946-1958 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 6.
      - Exchange of stock, 1963 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 7.
      - Pensions, 1956-1965 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 8.
      - Reorganization, 1957-1959 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 9.
      - Reorganization, 1961-1965 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 10.
    - India
      - Correspondence, 1960-1966 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 11.
      - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 12.
    - Italy (Milan)
      - David James correspondence, 1951-1953 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 13.
    - Netherlands (Amsterdam)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1965, 2 folders (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 14.
    - Portugal (Lisbon)
      - Correspondence, 1961 (Box RS2)
    - South Africa
      - Correspondence, 1961 (Box RS2)
      - Donald Foote files, 1934-1943 (Box RS2)
        Items pulled from Box 17.
  - Chronological Files Series
    - 1954-1964 (Box RS2)
      Items pulled from Box 28-37.
    - 1965-1971 (Box RS3)
      Items pulled from Boxes 38-43.
  - Legal Files Series
    - Kohl, Howard, 1938-1939 (Box RS3)
      Items pulled from Box 45.
    - Lawsuits--Laemmar & Sartoris
      - Hugh F. Parker materials, 1961-1971 (Box RS3)
        Items pulled from Box 50.
      - Salary and financial data of Jack Laemmar, 1971 (Box RS3)
      - Salary and financial data of Ada Sartoris, 1971 (Box RS3)
    - Television
      - Correspondence, Volume I, 1944-1945 (Box RS3)
        Items pulled from Box 61.
      - Eastman Kodak
        - J.K. McEldowney correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box RS3)
        - Oriental International Films, 1948-1958, 5 folders (Box RS3)
          Items pulled from Boxes 62-63.
      - Facilities, 1949-1951, 2 folders (Box RS3)
        Items pulled from Boxes 63-64.
      - Ford Motor Company
        - James Melton Package, 1951 (Box RS3)
          Items pulled from Box 64.
  - Financial Files Series
    - Salaries, 1945 (Box RS3)
      Items pulled from Box 76.
  - Personnel Files Series
    - Military leaves of absence, 1968-1971 (Box RS3)
    - Personnel lists, Detroit, 1946 (Box RS3)
      Items pulled from Box 77.
    - Physical examination for executives, 1950-1967 (Box RS3)